{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Kitchen \u0026 Bath Resurfacing Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/40374/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40374,"taskName":"Bathtub or Other Bath or Kitchen Surface - Resurface or Reface","taskDescription":"Resurface or Reface a Bathtub or Other Bath or Kitchen Surface","xmTaskDescriptor":"Kitchen \u0026 Bath Resurfacing Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1203,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Bathtub statically electro object metal","textMessagingName":"Resurf Tub/Kitchen","rolloverLongDesc":"This specialty service completely recoats porcelain fixtures with a finish of any color. While not as durable as the original finish, it does allow people to dramatically improve the appearance of something like a bathtub, without the large headache \u0026 expense of replacing it. Some kitchen appliances may also be resurfaced in this way.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes bathtubs, sinks, toilets \u0026 some appliances.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Resurface or Reface a Bathtub or Other Bath or Kitchen Surface.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Bathtub Resurfacing \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Kitchen Counters: Resurface \u0026 Reface","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":27,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Bathtub or Other Surface Resurfacing","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Bathtub or Other Bath or Kitchen Surface - Resurface or Reface","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Bathtub Liner / Shower Surround Project","urlName":"Bathtub-or-Other-Bath-or-Kitchen-Surface-Resurface-or-Reface","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Bathtub Resurfacing Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"electrostatic, powdercoating,coating,coat, Bath,Surface,tub,Resurface,countertops, kitchen, reglaze","emcCategoryOid":-12059,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":668,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40374/":{"taskOID":40374,"originalTaskOID":40374,"setID":668,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5409,"questionDisplayText":"Item(s) to be Resurfaced","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which fixtures or surfaces require resurfacing? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1612,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Contemporary bathtub","answerDisplayText":"Contemporary bathtub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":985,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom sink","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":791,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Antique bathtub","answerDisplayText":"Antique bathtub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3425,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Kitchen sink","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5649,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Shower stall","answerDisplayText":"Shower stall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6765,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wall tile","answerDisplayText":"Wall tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5645,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Shower Pan","answerDisplayText":"Shower Pan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1663,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Countertop tile","answerDisplayText":"Countertop tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3416,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Kitchen appliance(s)","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen appliance(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1662,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6949,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Whirlpool tub","answerDisplayText":"Whirlpool tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5411,"questionDisplayText":"Needs to be Done","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be done? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5201,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Repair cracks and chips","answerDisplayText":"Repair cracks and chips","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5331,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Resurface in same color","answerDisplayText":"Resurface in same color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5330,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Resurface in new color","answerDisplayText":"Resurface in new color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3779,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Match to other features in room","answerDisplayText":"Match to other features in room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5409,"questionDisplayText":"Item(s) to be Resurfaced","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which fixtures or surfaces require resurfacing? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1612,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Contemporary bathtub","answerDisplayText":"Contemporary bathtub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":985,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom sink","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":791,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Antique bathtub","answerDisplayText":"Antique bathtub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3425,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Kitchen sink","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5649,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Shower stall","answerDisplayText":"Shower stall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6765,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wall tile","answerDisplayText":"Wall tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5645,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Shower Pan","answerDisplayText":"Shower Pan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1663,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Countertop tile","answerDisplayText":"Countertop tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3416,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Kitchen appliance(s)","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen appliance(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1662,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6949,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Whirlpool tub","answerDisplayText":"Whirlpool tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1612,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Contemporary bathtub","answerDisplayText":"Contemporary bathtub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":985,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom sink","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":791,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Antique bathtub","answerDisplayText":"Antique bathtub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3425,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Kitchen sink","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5649,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Shower stall","answerDisplayText":"Shower stall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6765,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wall tile","answerDisplayText":"Wall tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5645,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Shower Pan","answerDisplayText":"Shower Pan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1663,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Countertop tile","answerDisplayText":"Countertop tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3416,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Kitchen appliance(s)","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen appliance(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1662,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6949,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Whirlpool tub","answerDisplayText":"Whirlpool tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5411,"questionDisplayText":"Needs to be Done","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be done? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5201,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Repair cracks and chips","answerDisplayText":"Repair cracks and chips","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5331,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Resurface in same color","answerDisplayText":"Resurface in same color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5330,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Resurface in new color","answerDisplayText":"Resurface in new color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3779,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Match to other features in room","answerDisplayText":"Match to other features in room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5201,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Repair cracks and chips","answerDisplayText":"Repair cracks and chips","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5331,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Resurface in same color","answerDisplayText":"Resurface in same color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5330,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Resurface in new color","answerDisplayText":"Resurface in new color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3779,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Match to other features in room","answerDisplayText":"Match to other features in room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}